browsec.com 2019-12-11

# Browsec VPN - Privacy Policy

June 26, 2015

This privacy policy sets forth how Browsec, LLC collects and processes personal information from any user of our services, as well as our use and disclosure of such information.

When you use our service, you agree to let us process your information as we describe in this Privacy Policy statement.

  1. ## Collection of personal information

    1. ###  Personal information 

«Personal information» means any information that identifies you, this includes information provided by you when using our services.

    2. ###  Cookies 

When you visit browsec.com website, we may store one or more cookies — a small text string — on your computer. These cookies can be persistent, that is, they may remain after you close your browser window. Please refer to your browser’s «Help» for information on removing cookies.

    3. ###  Account information 

When you create your Browsec account, we provide you with an anonymous Account ID that is permanently stored in your web browser. You may also link additional information to your account, such as your e-mail address.

    4. ###  Operational data 

To ensure the continuous delivery of our Services, we have to automatically record some information from your web browser additional/or client software. The information does not identify the User personally. Browsec uses such information in the aggregate for various purposes, including the monitoring of the service.

  2. ## Use of Personal Information

    1. ###  Use 

Browsec may use automatically-collected information in the aggregate for the purpose of monitoring, research or analysis. The information is collected only when the Browsec service is currently active.

    2. ###  Disclosure 

Browsec does not disclose your Personal information unless it is required by the legal law enforcement requests.

  3. ## Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may need to update the Privacy Policy from time to time. Your continued use of the Service after the effective date of such changes constitutes your acceptance of such changes. The effective date will be reflected in the «last modified» notice above.

  4. ## Contact information

If you have any questions or comments about our Privacy Policy, please contact us at [support@browsec.com](mailto:support@browsec.com).
